[Instrumental music]
Let’s look at the four roles in guteneo and what each one can do.
The administrator manages the workspace. They prepare and approve outgoing messages, and view reports.
A supervisor prepares messages for sending. Approval and access to reports are separate permissions, both disabled by default.
The operator imports documents and prepares messages for sending. They cannot approve them.
An observer can view documents, recipients and delivery updates. They cannot change anything in the workspace or approve a message.
In the standard workflow, an authorised person approves the delivery in the browser.
[The instrumental music continues.]
[A final chord resonates, without percussion.]
[The music gently fades away.]